Hi, thanks for joining us. You're
watching Drogram. Uh we're here Monday
through Friday every day starting today.
I'm Ted R, editorial cartoonist. John
Kuryaku, CIA whistleblower is here with
me as well. We had a good fun weekend
hanging out together. Thanks everyone
for joining. Please like, follow, and sh
and share the show. Uh we are really
appreciative of your support and uh we
still need more of it. If you haven't
done so already, please consider
migrating over to Rumble where we really
do make a lot more money. A lot of
people are watching us both. Uh, you
know, just keep one screen open and
watch the other one and you'd be amazed
at how much good that does us. We need
those watch hours over on Rumble. Um,
it's it's going to make this viable for
us. Um, all right. So, what's on the
agenda? Among other things, we'll be
answering your questions as always. Um,
we have the uh, of course, obviously the
latest from Ukraine. A lot to talk about
there. Democrats are back in Texas. Uh,
Trump, I don't know. He's trying to
eliminate all the ways that we know how
to vote. Uh, he doesn't like mailin
ballots and he doesn't like voting
machines. I guess pigeons are next. Uh,
Newsmax has to shell out $67 million to
Dominion, meaning that if you get
defamed, but you have deep corporate
pockets, you can probably prevail in
court. Um, MSNBC is changing their name.
Paris is getting ready for 50 degrees
Celsius days um in the near future uh
because of climate change in Europe.
We'll talk about what that means. Iran
has arrested or detained over 20,000
people suspected of possibly spying for
Israel. We'll get into that. That seems
like a lot of spies, but John, spying is
is your thing. Um yeah, is
>> Israel is uh Israel is increasingly
isolated. Um a parent an accused
pedophile. um has just been uh allowed
to flee to Israel. This is the second
this has happened before and I guess it
will happen again, but uh people are
paying more attention than they usually
do. And Israel's plan to take over Gaza
City couldn't be worse timed because
Hamas has just agreed to a 60-day
ceasefire uh just minutes ago and to
release all of the hostages. So, what
shall we do first?
>> Oh my god. Well, first I want to say
what a good time I had hanging out with
with Ted and uh and those close to him
over the weekend. We had a we had a nice
lunch. I went to this uh hacker
conference and and gave a short talk
there. But when I got back home, Ted, by
by Amtrak yesterday afternoon,
>> as soon as I stepped outside of
Washington's Union Station, I'm greeted
by two enormous armored personnel
carriers pointed at the train station
along with an armored Humvey with a 50
caliber machine gun mounted on it. Why?
What is the purpose of having armored
personnel carriers and mounted 50
caliber guns? The purpose is to kill
people.
Okay. I mean, otherwise, what do you
need those kinds of things for? They're
to kill people. To make matters even
worse, and I actually couldn't hold my
tongue. I had to shout some epithets. Uh
there were people, and I'm going to say
pointedly, of all races, there were
people taking pictures and posing with
the National Guardsmen.
It enraged me.
Uh, but it's not just at Union Station,
Ted. It's all the way up and down 14th
Street. It's on the US Street corridor.
It's in Georgetown in the center of
Georgetown in front of the two-story
Barnes & Noble. This is not where we
have crime in Washington DC.
>> It's in
>> We have crime in southeast and in upper
northwest Washington and even southeast
southeast east of the Anacostia River.
There are very specific areas that are
of Washington. They're dangerous and
these National Guardsmen at all are not
in those areas.
>> John, the visual that you gave me just
now of the uh of the uh people taking
selfies with basically this fascist
light kind of thing, you know, reminds
me of the clash lyric uh if uh Hitler
came to the airport, they'd still send
today they'd still send a limousine
anyway. I mean, you know, it's like
people are just, you know, resistance
doesn't come naturally, especially not
to the American people.
>> Dad, I was watching, I'm sorry to
interrupt. I was watching a documentary
yesterday on um on Albert Anastasia, uh
former crime boss who was nicknamed the
Lord High Executioner for all the people
that he killed. And uh he was finally
put away by uh by uh then district
attorney uh Dwey who then became the
governor of New York, Tom Thomas Dwey.
And then he ran for president against
both Franklin Roosevelt and um and Harry
Truman nearly beating Harry Truman. You
remember Truman holding up the Chicago
Tribune saying Dwey beats Truman. Dwey
defeats Truman. Well, the conclusion
that they came that they came to about
that 1948 election was only because uh
was only that Dwey lost because he had a
short cropped mustache and it reminded
people of Adolf Hitler because people
Americans were so anti-fascist.
So anti-fascist that they wouldn't even
vote for a guy who had a mustache.
>> That's so we changed.
>> We We have changed. And poor Thomas
Dwey. Well, I mean, he does have the New
York State throughway named after him
today. So, he does. He does.
>> It's not the worst thing in the world.
>> And you know what? He he was asked by
Richard Nixon, I didn't know this till
yesterday. He was asked by Richard Nixon
in 1969 if he would become the uh the uh
chief justice of the Supreme Court and
he turned it down.
>> How come?
>> Um he said that he just wasn't really
interested. He was 67 at the time and he
had had a good life and he was calling
it a career.
Can you imagine in this day and age?
He's a child. Um, yeah, that's uh that's
that is that is super cool. Just want to
thank uh over on Rumble, thank you for
two Toa for becoming a monthly supporter
and watching us both on Rumble and
YouTube. So, we we appreciate you. Thank
you so much.
>> Thank you for that.
>> And yeah, I mean obviously like the 50
cal is uh as David Wagner says is not
much of a crime deterrent, right? That's
not what this is about. This is about
normalizing the militarization
of uh American city streets. I mean,
I've said it before, I'm going to say it
again, but that's what this is. It's
about making the abnormal normal,
something that people are used to in
other countries, but not here.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Um, all right. So, what should we talk
about first? Should we get into the
should we into Ukraine?
>> Yeah, let's talk about Ukraine. All of
Washington's on edge today. Uh even even
the bridges into and out of town were
were closed today uh just because so
many important leaders are in in town
for this meeting that's taking place
right now as we speak. Uh meeting
between Donald Trump uh Zalinski,
the head of NATO, the head of the EU,
the chancellor of Germany, the prime
minister of the UK, prime minister of uh
of Italy, the president of France, and
the president of Finland. They're all
here in Washington. They all seem to be
very politely pushing back on Donald
Trump. U Trump has shifted his position,
of course, which we would all expect him
to do. He's he's shifted his position on
whether or not a ceasefire is a
prerequisite for actually coming to an
agreement. It was until it wasn't, and
now it's not. Um, but he still maintains
that he believes we're going to have at
least the outline of a deal by Friday,
whether the Ukrainians like it or not.
But here's the key, and this is where
it's it's especially um confusing.
Witito said today, Whitoff the special
envoy said today said this afternoon
that the Russians had agreed to allow
Ukraine to become what we call for other
countries a major non-NATO ally. So it
would have the same status as Japan, as
South Korea, as Saudi Arabia and Bahrain
and Kuwait. They're not members of NATO,
but they get the same benefits as if
they were members of NATO.
The Russian foreign ministry came out
immediately and said that is absolutely
untrue. We never agreed to major
non-NATO status for Ukraine. But then
the Kremlin came out and said now wait a
minute we haven't taken a position
>> yet on major non-NATO status for
Ukraine. So even the Russians appear to
be a little bit
uncertain as to what exactly their
position happens to be. Which reminds us
that Russia is not as much of an
autocracy as the American media might
like to tell us.
>> Oh, Ted, I had to I had to shut off Oh
my god. I had to shut off MSNBC. I I
just couldn't do it anymore. It's as
it's like it's like a neofascist
uh uh network. It's incredible. They
want war so badly
>> and they want a coup so badly in Russia
that they just can't contain themselves.
Then I switched it to CNN. They're
almost as bad, but I think they hide it
a little bit better. So then I had to
switch to Fox, which much to my surprise
is like, well, you know, let's wait and
see how things play out.
>> A little more reasonable.
>> Yeah. Uhhuh. Crazy.
>> Yeah. It's it's it's it's it's wacky
world for sure. Um, you know, but John,
uh, the New York Times rep reported
today that the Kremlin had offered, um,
to allow, uh, you know, article five
like protections to, um, to Ukraine
under US and European protection a year
ago. I'm like, John, did I miss that?
Did I sleep late one morning and just
not take the times that morning or did
that did that happen? Or, you know what
I mean? Like, what's going on? Did that
happen? I don't remember it.
>> I don't remember it either, to tell you
the truth. I I'm not sure what the heck
is going on.
>> I mean, you know, at the New York Times,
they have a lot of 28-y olds writing for
them these days.
>> That's true. That's true. And, you know,
we're in this weird period where it's as
though you can't take anybody seriously.
Um, you don't know who's taking what
position or they take a position and
they deny having taken it or their
position changes. Mhm. I I don't know.
You look at the Washington Post today.
You remember what a big deal it was,
Ted, when when Jeff Bezos said that
we're not going to write um op-eds or or
uh editorials anymore on ABC, ABC, C,
and D issues because everybody has a
position, so we don't care anymore.
Well, now the editorial page is
completely right-wing. All
>> completely totally right-wing. It's like
looking at the New York Post
>> and Well and and insanely corporatist.
Um, a day or two ago, the Washington
Post editorial board weighed in on
driverless cars in Boston.
>> What? and and said yeah and said that
it's that and basically made fun of
Bostononians who said who were against
it saying that they're a bunch of of
lites and it's time to get with it and
uh dismissing the concerns that they
basically had the gall in the editorial
to say well they've already proven
themselves in Tucson so Boston shouldn't
be a problem I don't know if Jeff Bezos
has ever been to Boston but I would say
those two cities don't look anything
alike
>> nothing at all
>> I mean Boston is an organic old city
with twisty tiny little narrow streets
uh and lots of double parking and
extremely aggressive driving. Um you
know that the term mass hole comes from
there. Um you know it's like I always
tell people like in New York people are
bluffing and they're pretending like
they're going to hit you. In Boston
they're going to hit you. Um but yeah,
so it it was just funny like why is the
Washington Post editorial board
interested in this? And I was like, I
even commented on their comment section.
Jeff, is that you?
>> Oh my god.
>> I mean, it's got to be like some, you
know, investment of his. Uh, it's got to
be,
>> you know, there there's got to be a
corporate interest there.
>> Um,
>> so let's talk about that um article 5
thing, right? Yeah. Okay. So,
>> I understand why Japan would have that
status without being a NATO because
Japan's not in not in the North
Atlantic. It's in the North Pacific. But
why would a why would Ukraine want want
how why would it receive sort of NATO
like privileges without being in NATO?
And why would Russia agree to it? I'm
kind of leaning toward believing that
they are agreeing to it. Is this just a
way for Russia to save face?
>> Yes, I think that's exactly what it is.
I think that's exactly what it is. And
if the Russians want the
um if the Russians want the territory
that everybody says they want, uh
they're going to have to give up some
major concession. And that major
concession has to be this non-NATO
uh ally status. So
>> of all the of all of Russia's demands, I
mean besides the territory obviously,
which ain't nothing. Yeah. Um you know,
we we are talking about taking over a
fifth of a country.
>> Yeah. It is% a big country. Um, it's not
like taking a fifth of of of Likenstein,
right? Um, but it's like still, uh, you
know, you're talking about a lot. Um, I
mean, to me, of all of Putin's demands,
>> the NATO things seemed the most
obviously reasonable. If I were the
president of the Russian Federation, I
wouldn't want a NATO power. a hair
trigger World War I 1914 style alliances
on away on my very sensitive border
where people came across less than a
century ago and killed 30 million of my
people.
>> That's right. I I couldn't agree more.
>> See, and then that that just leads me to
believe what you just alluded to that
the two countries aren't exactly as far
apart as as most people think. That a
lot of this is posturing.
Mhm. Uh, Soden 2324
on YouTube is asking us, "Why is our
foreign policy so trash? And where, and
by the way, thanks for the donation. And
where and when did our foreign policy go
out the window?" It's a little vague,
but um, John,
>> well, you remember you remember the old
saying that foreign policy differences
end at the shore,
and they don't end at the shore anymore.
And I'll tell you who changed that was
N. Gingrich in 199 1995
when when he came out and just
eviscerated uh the Clinton
administration on on everything. It was
on on everything that they stood for. He
fought them over. And so I'm I'm
wondering if uh if that's the norm now.
I mean we've gone 30 years with these
major changes in foreign policy. um and
uh and these major differences in
foreign policy and do we just have to
accept it?
>> It is a realignment, right? I mean,
there's also a dramatic political
realignment uh that followed. I mean,
there's a lot of different things going
on, right? I think it's a perfect storm.
There's also
>> uh in order to fill the gap sort of
meanwhile, the Republican party has
become what they used to call it more
isolationist. Yeah.
>> God bless them. I'm I'm all I'm all for
it. Yeah, I am too.
>> And uh you know, but I think the U I
mean, if you go back to I I guess I
would argue that US foreign policy has
been inc basically aggressive for well
over a hundred years, ever since
Theodore Roosevelt. And um
>> it's gotten more so all the time. And
basically, Congress keeps abdicating
their war powers, responsibility. I
mean, just the fact that like, you know,
in one of the the back of one of my
lists, uh, books, the anti-American
manifesto, I put I published one of
those lists of every US military
intervention. I actually couldn't do
them all because there were too many to
like even in tiny type to put them all
in there, but I put in a lot of them and
yeah, we've only declared war five
times. That tells you that we're not
that that that the separation of powers
isn't working and that we have an
imperial presidency.
>> Absolutely true.
>> And they get in there. I think, you
know, I think what happens with
presidents also is that they love to do
foreign policy and start wars and stuff.
It makes them feel important. Uh it's
the one thing that they can really
control. Like a president can say, "John
Kuryaku, you go out to, you know, Syria
and you do this and you can have this
resource and you get it and you don't
have he doesn't have to ask permission
from anyone." But like nothing domestic
is like that.
>> Yeah. Nothing domestic is like that.
You're exactly right. There were a
couple of other things too, Ted, that
that I heard today. Um, and it's funny,
I heard them like not as major
announcement announcements, but just as
a sides. The one was the major non-NATO
ally status, but the other one was what
the Russians really really want is a
land bridge through Crimea.
>> Mhm.
>> Right. Okay. That's that's actually a
big ask and uh and it's an important
ask. So why are we not talking about it?
Why are none of the networks talking
about it? That this may be the lynch pin
to an agreement as a land bridge.
>> I don't think the networks, aside from
being biased, I'm not sure they really
even understand
>> understand. And you know what? It's
funny. They have like the former US
ambassador to Ukraine. They have Ron
McCall, the former US ambassador to
Russia. They had John Bolton, who's been
on every network today. Well, he hasn't
been on Fox because they hate him, but
he's been on all the other networks. Um,
and nobody is making the analogy
with the land bridge that connected West
Germany with West Berlin. It's been done
before.
>> It's doable and they're not talking
about it.
>> And there's lots of precedents in
history, right? Germany wanted to have a
land bridge to the city of Danzig that
was separated by from from Poland. Um,
you know, I mean, when uh Pakistan
became independent, East Pakistan was
separated by hundreds of miles from
Pakistan proper. Yeah. That didn't work
out. Now, when we theorized about a
Palestinian state, you know, that we
have to have a lands bridge between Gaza
and um and and the West Bank, I mean,
you have you're going to have to. It
doesn't make any sense. Um
>> you're going to have to
>> It's as simple as that. It's as simple
as that. See, again, now, forgive me.
I'm in a little bit of a bad mood today.
I'm not feeling very well.
>> I'm sorry.
>> No, thank you. It's I got my last uh
blood transfusion and I'm supposed to be
feeling great and I feel terrible. But
anyway, um
if this were any other time, if this
were any other administration,
we would go on to whatever our preferred
news network happened to be and we would
see charts and graphs. This is what they
want. This is what the counter offer is,
right? This is what's being discussed
today.
>> Uh this is
>> and this is why each side wants what
they want.
>> Exactly.
>> We're getting none of it. All we're
getting
>> there's no analysis.
>> No, there's no analysis at all. We're
getting these biased talking heads going
everywhere and saying this is a terrible
deal. Like for example, when I when I
turned on MSNBC midday today, all they
wanted to talk about was how just the
act of meeting Putin and when Trump put
his hand on top of Putin's hand that
weakened America. They said,
>> "I felt America get a little weaker that
second. Like my cat shuddered at that
exact moment."
>> The clouds clouds covered the sun. They
shook hands and then Trump went like
this with his hand on top of Putin's. It
weakened America.
>> Voldemort got a little stronger at that
moment.
>> Oh my god. I I know. It's so stupid.
It's it's it's literally akin to the to
the logic that a uh that a gay marriage
weakened traditional marriage. Like
>> Exactly.
>> Two dudes down the street being married
that that messes up your marriage,
>> right? No, divorce weakens marriage.
Divorces Not gays.
>> No, that's true. Oh my god.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, so there's no analysis.
There's there's nobody that's, you know,
giving a a considered position uh any
any insight into what this may mean a
week from now or a month from now. I'll
say my own analysis is, and I'm not
saying this for for selfish reasons. I'm
saying it because I I believe it. I'm
impressed by Donald Trump's flexibility.
I really am. Well, I'm impressed that
he's willing to talk, that he's been
willing to come back to it even after
being disappointed and maybe perhaps
disgusted uh by what he thought was
entransigence on both sides. Um, you
know, and of course I think we should
take note of the fact that we had this
this was a doover this this meeting with
Zilinski. Same room, same gold chair,
>> same camera angles,
>> same c same dude, right? Same same. But
this time, Silinski comes proper, much
better dressed, you know, brought his he
wore a
>> suit like thing. Not really a
>> It was a Regis Philin suit is what it
was,
>> right? Or like a
>> black pants, black jacket, black shirt,
black tie.
>> Yeah, I kind of like that look
personally. Yeah, I I it's it's a little
bit odds, but uh I I actually like it.
>> Although Although for a small man like
him, it doesn't make a lot of sense.
It's better for a tall guy like me
because it slims me down. Yeah.
>> Um but whatever. It worked. He looked
great.
>> Um he looked a lot better than usual.
There was even a comment about it and a
joke about it. There were laughs all
around, smiles all around. JD, who
clearly can't stand Zalinski or the
Ukrainian cause, he he he
zipped it. He had nothing to say. And so
his silence was super loud. Um, so it
was all it was all loves and love and
kisses. The Euros were supposedly
providing backup, but that doesn't make
any sense. Um, and anyway, but even
their presence, you know, kind of like
helps bring get it done. I mean, I'm
really optimistic. I think there's going
to be a uh, you know, I'm going to go
out on a limb and say I think there's
going to be a trilateral meeting between
uh, Trump, Zilinsky, and Putin later
this week, just the way Trump wants.
>> It's going to have to be. That's right.
>> And I think they're going to bang it
out.
>> Yep. Yep. Without
>> All right. So, here, let's let's get to
brass tax, John. Um, so Russia's going
to sort of say we won because, you know,
they Ukraine didn't join NATO. They
didn't join NATO. They just got all the
benefits of being in NATO.
>> Um,
>> which is good enough for them.
>> If that's good enough for them, that's
good enough for me. Um, then they keep
they keep Crimea. It's recognized as
annexed. Now, here's the question. The
Dawnboss, which I've always argued they
shouldn't have wanted in the first place
because it only gave them trouble.
>> But, right,
>> but like they had it. Okay, I understand
no one wants Personally, if I were
Lincoln, I would have let the
Confederacy go. That's my mentality. Um,
but he's they they they it's going to be
is that going to be a dotted line where
Ukraine formerly believes that that's
their their formal status is that's part
of Ukraine. We never admit that it's
gone. It's like Kurdistan or is it a is
it is it a is it a a frozen conflict
like a line of control between India and
Pakistan or is it
>> truly recognized on as an international
border by the West as part of Russia?
I think it's one of these situations,
Ted, where where it all remains to be
seen. I'm not even sure the
administration knows exactly what it
wants to do here. It's waiting to see
how much success it might have by the
end of the week because, as you said, it
looks like we're coming up on a
trilateral meeting, US, Russia, Ukraine,
that could be held as soon as Friday. Uh
Trump made a major concession to the
Russians this morning when he said that
peace talks do not have to come after a
ceasefire.
>> He doesn't want a ceasefire. He views it
as a waste of time.
>> And he said that the Russians and
Ukrainians can beat the hell out of each
other while we talk about a settlement.
That's a new position.
>> He never said that before.
>> You know, I'm you know, it's funny. I
don't disagree with President Trump on
this. Um, you know, you and I have seen
millions of ceasefires in our lives and
they're very problematic. I mean,
basically, it's always like someone
always breaks it and it's always it you
end up with a ton of squabbbling. He
broke it. No, they broke it. And and
it's like it's like dealing with unruly
kids in the backseat of the station
wagon. And in the end and and while
you're hashing out that crap, you're not
getting down to brass tax and and and
actually trying to solve, as Putin would
say, the root causes of the conflict.
>> That's right. I think that's exactly it.
I think that's exactly it.
>> So, what concessions does Ukraine get?
Well, obviously they're getting the
they're going to get that NATO
protection, which is what they wanted
all along.
>> Yes, it is. And nobody has said anything
yet, but I think they also get fasttrack
membership into the European Union,
which is going to change everything.
Remember, Ukraine has Ukraine has
probably more wheat
than any country on Earth but the United
States and Russia. And so much of that
wheat goes to Europe and Africa, Western
Europe and Africa. They can sell their
wheat unencumbered. They can sell their
natural gas unencumbered. They have
trillions of dollars worth of rare earth
metals. they can sell it, you know, to
the United States. And um economically,
this is going to be a very big deal for
Ukraine. I don't think the Russians care
if Ukraine is in the European Union.
>> Since we are returning to 20th century
type Yalta style negotiations, could
could there be reparations? Um you know,
for example, might Russia be asked to uh
you know, pay Ukraine for damage to
property? Might Russia ask the United
States for compensation for Nordstrom,
too?
Nordstream, too.
>> You know, I wouldn't be uh surprised,
but I wouldn't be surprised also if the
Russians just told them there won't be
any reparations.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Just like the Germans told the
Greeks, "Yeah, no reparations. We're
we're broke. The Allies bombed us into
dust. No reparations." And here we are
70 Is it 70? It's 80 years now after the
the war. And the Greeks are like, "Where
are reparations?
You You Germans still haven't paid us.
We want our money.
>> I I like I like the Greek style. I like
I like I like that museum they built for
the Elgen marbles, too.
>> Yes.
>> It's a very nice museum.
>> World class museum.
>> Beautiful museum. The Brits really can't
argue that the Greeks are too unruly to
take care of their stuff anymore.
>> Oh, that's what they used to argue.
>> Yes.
>> It's like uh the uncivilized Greeks.
That's a hilarious oxymoron. Um but uh
okay so let's uh we don't we're we're
let's see we're let's talk about Oh well
you mentioned MSNBC this might be a good
time to talk about that do a little
media stuff. So MSNBC
split off from NBC proper.
>> So as part of that deal um the corporate
the corporate entity that now is going
to be running MSNBC or NBC has asked
that MS not take its NBC with it. So,
it's just going to be MS now.
>> Um, so my for people who are
>> young, uh, this was a partnership
between Microsoft and NBC years and
years ago. It stopped being that.
Microsoft dropped out years and years
>> years ago.
>> It's a legacy thing. It's just like
Microsoft's like whatever. You can It's
sort of like uh the city bike rental
system here in New York.
>> City bike hasn't had anything to do with
it in years. It's run by Lyft now
>> inexplicably. Yes.
>> But it's just a legacy thing. So, all
right. Well, they're also talking about
pivoting to the right, right? They want
to become a more centrist
uh network.
>> Maybe. Maybe.
>> That's what they say. Maybe
>> the the Daily Beast
>> You and I both know the history of this.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. It doesn't work. The
Daily Beast has the the most interesting
take on this. Um and the Daily Beast,
they were kind of dicks about about it.
the way the they wrote about it. They
said that that NBC
>> um sent around an email like to to every
journalist in the world who covers media
and said that MSNBC is going to change
the name. It's going to drop the the NBC
to split it off. Um, and it's going to
be MS Now, but you are not allowed to
call it MS Now in the articles that you
write until you first call it the My
Source News Opinion World Network and
then you can say that my source news
opinion world stands for MS Now
and you it's it says um they may say
this only if they include a space in the
middle of the acronym MS space Now, it
is unclear if the name is supposed to be
written in bold type face as well as
Trump style all caps, but the CEO of the
new parent company, Versent, Mark
Lazarus, used the same bold and all caps
formulation in a memo that he sent to
staff, which was then sent to the Daily
Beast. And a spokesman declined to
comment on whether you could call it MS
now, but M period, S period, capital N,
little O, little W. So, people are
having a little bit of fun.
>> Miz now.
>> Miz now. It's a stupid name. The MS
doesn't make any sense.
>> No.
>> Um, nobody cares really what it stands
for. You can just keep it MSNBC and
nobody still is going to care. Um, the
the brass say it's going to try to move
to the center. Um, Rachel Matto said,
"Oh, no, it's not. They're not they're
apparently not changing any of the
talent. It's all the same." unwatchable
shows that it is now.
>> So I I don't know what the what the
point is.
>> Yeah. Thank you, Nanzene. Nonzi's right.
You see that?
>> And so is Tusk. It could be multiple
sclerosis now. It could be more [__]
now.
Yes. I like that.
>> Multiple sclerosis. Those are correct.
>> I feel like that's cruel to multiple
sclerosis. What did multiple sclerosis
do to deserve that?
>> That's right. We we shouldn't uh
>> Yes. You're right.
>> But I mean, so okay, so first of all,
just Yeah, let's let's just first of
all, it is a centrist
>> corporist network as it is.
>> It is.
>> But but there's no but I know what they
mean. And you know, look, MSNBC has
they've been down this road before. They
started out as a centrist as a
centerright network. Then they went
center. Then they became what they are
today, a de a democ well slightly more
dem uh to the left of the Democratic
party back when Phil Donahghue was on.
>> Then they they got rid of people like
him and uh Ed Schultz and people like
that. Um and then they moved
>> and Brian Becker and Jesse Ventura.
>> Correct. And then they ended up uh as a
basically um what we know between now
and then. And it's just been basically
been MSDNC ever since. And I mean, look,
they're not doing great in the in the
ratings now, but they were doing worse
before
>> when they were going with for the for
the corpor high corporatist
>> approach. So, they've got to look back
and just know that's not going to work.
>> I mean, that's CNN is dying over the in
that in that same space. That's a lane
you don't want to be swimming in.
>> Dying. And I'll tell you, Ted, when I
woke up this morning and I read this in
the New York Times and then I went
around and looked at it uh at different
accounts of it, I thought there's
literally nothing in this announcement
that is going to make me want to watch
MSNBC.
Nothing.
>> No.
>> Talk about corporatist. You might as
well call it MSDNC, which is what a lot
of people do call it.
>> It is so [__] boring. I mean,
whatever you think of Fox, and look, I
don't share their politics. It's
entertaining, you know, and and like
they get that. And that's why, you know,
you're running content for 24 hours a
day and you want people to stick around,
you better be entertaining. Um, and I
don't think there's anything wrong with
being entertaining uh at all. It's I'm
not against that. Not like, you know,
here's your oatmeal, take your medicine,
whatever, eat your spinach. Uh, it's
it's just it's uh I don't know. I I
think I don't know. Is it too early to
say it's the beginning of the end for MS
now or is it Ted because they're going
in a bad way?
>> Well, NBC won't even allow them to use
the Peacock logo anymore. And I think
that's actually kind of a big deal. They
said that they wanted to keep the
Peacock and uh NBC said, "Well, no,
because the Peacock has been associated
with NBC for the last hundred years. So,
you guys are going to have to come up
with your own uh your own logo." And
it's funny, another thing is that that
they MS now is becoming a part of this
new company being spun off called
Versent Vers N. That's going to include
CNBC, which all right makes sense. But
it's going to include the Golf Channel,
some network I never heard of called
Sports Engine, and own the Oprah Winfrey
network.
>> Oh man, it's a What's that?
>> It's a box of misfit toys.
>> That's exactly what it And that makes me
think that that they're preparing the
public for these networks just to go
away eventually.
>> The Oprah Winfrey Network. Oh my god.
>> Um, yeah.
>> You know, let me add something about
Phil Donahghue. Rebellious Rainbow
Unicorn says, "I was too young to
realize how progressive Phil Donahghue
was." I'll tell you something about Phil
Donahghue. I always knew he was kind of
a kind of a good uh you know a good
lefty, but I never paid much attention.
And then when I got out of prison, I got
a call from Mark Ash at the uh Real uh
what was it called? Reader Supported
News. Reader supported News Network. And
he said, "Hey, do you want to write a
column for Reader Supported News?" I
said, "Yeah, I really need the money."
He said, "What's the Washington Post pay
you?" And I said, "Well, I've only
written two for the Post, but they give
me $400." and he said, "Um, okay, I'll
give you $400," which is a lot of money.
Was a lot of money for an op-ed in 2015.
And he paid me
$400 per oped
per week, right, for the next for the
next nine years.
And he told me finally after seven of
those years that he actually wasn't
paying me. Phil Donahghue was paying me.
>> Oh, wow.
>> That Phil Donaf Phil Donahghue felt bad
that I was broke and I'd been imprisoned
and my wife ran off and and it was just
this big,
>> you know,
[__] storm that fell on my head. And so,
Phil Donahghue put up 1600 bucks a month
to make sure that I didn't end up
sleeping in my car. That's what a good
guy he was.
>> I have a personal Phil Donahghue story.
So, Bill Donahghue started his career in
Dayton where I grew up
>> in Dayton.
>> He started in Dayton. Um, I didn't know
that. WHIO TV and uh that's so it was a
local talk show. It's the first place
I've ever been on TV. I was 10 or 11
years old. Uh I don't remember I don't
remember the context at all. Uh but you
know, he was he was super interesting
then. It was at the end of the Vietnam
War. He was an unabashed liberal from
day one. Uh in the old school, you know,
not the way liberals are kind of rancid
and at and war mockery and uh he uh
although obviously uh you know Tom Ler
kind of understood about liberals but um
but but still uh you know he was great.
Anyway, um after that incident, one day
um my mom and I are sit at home and
there's a knock on the back door and
who's at our back door but Phil
Donahghue. He's just had a He had a car
accident on Far Hills Avenue in Ketaring
near our house.
>> I I know Ketaring
>> and he needed to use the phone. There's
there's no cell phones. He's like, you
know, I need to call someone. So, my mom
went out on a couple of dates with him.
Um it didn't work out. Uh and he ended
up with Marlo Thomas. And uh I was like
I was like, "Mom, I mean mom was was
hot. My mom was hot and she was
definitely hot enough to go out with
Phil Donahghue. Uh but you know
obviously uh she wasn't she wasn't that
girl and uh you know so that that's it's
just a funny but he he seemed like a
very nice gentleman.
>> Yeah. What a what a gentleman he was.
Yeah. And and he stood up against the
Iraq war too. He he could have he could
have moderated his public position and
you know saved his show or whatever and
he didn't. No, he knew it was corporate
stupid [__] from the very beginning
and just c and just said it.
>> Yes.
>> He just he gave no shits.
>> That's right.
>> And probably he didn't think I mean that
was really interesting, right? Because
that was a period when um up until I
would say the 2000s, if you had the
ratings on American television or radio,
you could say anything you wanted and be
anything you wanted. You could have
hammers and sickles or swastikas or
anything you wanted. Didn't matter if
you had the ratings. Um,
>> look at the Morton Downey show.
>> That changed though. And uh, you know
what happened with uh with Phil? I guess
that was
>> 03 or 04.
>> He was he was you know I mean that was
he had the ratings and that was it kind
of blew my mind. And then uh Bill Maher
kind of got pushed out at ABC, but he
didn't really have great ratings when he
went when I was on when I was on talk
radio in LA. I got fired in I guess it
was 02 and it was when my station was
taken over by Clear Channel
Communications. I had the ratings. I had
the best ratings in the 26 year history
of the station for that time slot and
better than like better time slots. So I
thought I was really safe. My my station
manager said, "You're fine. you've got
the ratings, you're doing great. Um, I
was subbing in for uh, you know, Morning
Drive all the time and they they uh, but
then Clear Channel came along and they
said talk radio is inherently
right-wing,
>> so all liberals go. And I just I got the
act, you know, my my station manager,
David G. Hall at the time, he said,
"Don't worry, you know, you'll you're
going to land on your feet. You're going
to be get so many job offers." But the
industry was changing and radio was
starting to get disrupted by the
internet and you know obviously the
country was moving far further to the
right not not really the country but the
leadership class the elites and yeah
it's it's really interesting.
>> Wow man that is interesting
>> you know that's that would explain then
why air uh fell apart on SiriusXM radio.
That's where Rachel Matto got her start
and and everybody that listened to Air
America went because Bobby Kennedy Jr.
was on Air America with his own show and
he was quite progressive at the time
until he wasn't.
>> Well, I I did a lot of fill in on Air
America and uh in fact I I used to
co-host with Rachel in the morning
whenever her her uh her co-host was out.
So I I knew all about it. Um Air America
was very poorly run. It was run by this
kind of insane man. Um who basically his
whole idea was that it's all that
basically um it was about comedians, not
about serious analysis. So that's what
he hired, right? He had Jean uh Janine
Goff.
She was on Yeah.
>> who was adorable before she put on too
many tattoos. Um and uh you know there
was it's like and and she Al Franken was
the flagship of the show. um who I love
Al, but frankly he was a terrible host.
Um and uh there were and then there were
some of the lesser but basically the the
most talented ones were not being
promoted the most. And then you know
Rachel was the one who you could tell
she she could see what's going on and
she was looking for something better. Um
she was far much much more to the left
back then. Unabashedly progressive. I
mean you know
>> she's definitely not now. When my dad
when my when my son asked me what is a
sellout one time when he heard me use
the word I literally told him the story
of Rachel Maddau. I was like that's what
a that's what a sellout is.
>> Yeah.
Yeah. What a shame. And she is a
sellout.
>> She could have had class. She could have
been a contender as a certain movie
said. All right. So you wanted to talk
about uh oh we should also before we uh
move while we're in the media space.
>> John, what do you think about this uh
Newsmax settlement? Newsmax agreed to
pay three trenches totaling 67 million
bucks uh over basically saying that
Dominion's voting machines were uh
fixed. There was no evidence whatsoever
that they were. Um basically Newsmax and
right-wing media and Fox Fox already had
to pay out over this. Um has had to pay
out for smearing Newsmax uh sorry
smearing Dominion uh for saying that and
uh you know rightly so I think. Um, but
it seems like a steep Newsmax isn't that
big that they can afford $67 million,
are they?
>> Ted, no, they're not. Ted, have you been
to the Newsmax Studios here in
Washington?
>> No,
>> they're in they're in the Hall of States
building at 444 North Capitol Street or
444.
What is that? Yeah, North Capitol
Street. So NBC and MSNBC are on the
ground floor. Fox is on the fifth floor.
Uh PBS and Democracy Now are on the
sixth floor. Newsmax is in the basement
and it's lit it's literally a one room
studio. It's a nice studio. Artiz was
nicer, but it's it's small. There's a
little green room. There's a little
teeny weeny um makeup room.
>> Was really nice.
>> RT was was first class. They were in an
A-list building. It was really nice. And
it had the hottest ladies I've ever seen
in my life walking around there. I was
like, "What the hell?"
>> I just don't understand
where they're going to get this money
unless they get it from Chris um what's
his name? Christopher
uh the the owner
the owner of Newsmax. I forget his name.
Christopher Ruddy. Christopher Ruddy's a
billionaire who lives in um in Palm
Beach, very near Mara Lago. He's close
friends with Donald Trump. He's got
plenty of money in his own pockets,
>> but the LLC that is Newsbacks, I don't
know where they're going to get.
>> Yeah, they're going to they're going to
need an angel, right? Because I mean,
otherwise, this is going to be a Gawker
level extinction event. All right, let
me read an ad while we talk about that.
Set your clocks, mark your calendars,
and buckle up for the best NFL prime
time football action. Starting September
4th on Westwood One, you can catch all
the bone crushing hits last second hero
heroics and edge of your seat action
that NFL Thursday, Sunday, and Monday
nights have to offer. Whether you're
tailgating, driving, or chilling at
home, don't miss a single snap. Listen
on the NFL app, the Westwood One Sports
app, or Westwoodports.com,
or just say, "Alexa, open Westwood One
Sports." If it's the NFL, it's on
Westwood One.
>> Okay. So,
>> yeah, I'll do I'll do that.
>> All right. I'm not a football guy, but I
those who are should do that.
>> Um, West. So, so yeah. So, I mean,
Newsmax might be toast, right?
>> Newsmax is gonna have some problems.
Okay.
>> Yeah, they're going to have some
problems. Listen, they're very nice down
there. I've been on Newsmax three or
four times. They're always lovely
people, very nice. I enjoy their
company. Their politics are nutty.
They're told what to say, and they are
far to the right of Fox News. far to the
right. They're not as far as O, the One
America Network. They're just
>> nuts there. But they also have fewer
viewers than Al Jazzer America had when
they went uh kaput.
>> So O's not a a factor or player.
>> John, we've got a question from the
Rumble feed uh from uh deprogram show
feed a fan, sorry. um what whatever the
outcome of Russia Ukraine, there's going
to be ethnic cleansing in the disputed
territories, right?
>> I would uh I would think so. Yeah. The
Russians say that those disputed
territories are Russian. People there
are ethnically Russian. They speak
Russian at home. The schools teach in
Russian, so they're Russians. That's not
entirely true.
>> Not all.
>> No. No. My best friend from college, his
wife is from the Donbass. She's
ethnically Russian. She speaks Russian,
but by God, she considers herself to be
100% Ukrainian.
And so what? They're just going to
they're going to throw everybody out,
which of course is ethnic cleansing. My
guess is yes, that's that's what they
intend to do.
>> So it'll probably be like maybe not like
murders or like Gaza style at all, but
probably more like like what we saw in
um Negorno Carabach.
>> I I don't think so. Yeah.
>> Like an expulsion like, you know, just
for you to leave.
>> Yes. I think that's what we're going to
see.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so, all right. Well, that I mean that
and of course obviously violence usually
uh comes along with stuff like that uh
for because there's always stubborn
people who don't want to leave.
Understandably, it's
>> that's right
>> their house.
>> Uh no neck no neck Nick says, "Hey, I'm
the man with multiple chins." Uh says,
"John and Ted should have a show on Fox.
Two regular lefties on a right-wing
network helps the right view issues from
another point of view. I couldn't agree
more.
>> I'm loving that idea.
>> I would go on I would go work for Fox in
a second.
>> I I can go I can go put on a suit right
now.
>> Me, too.
>> That's what I Yeah, seriously.
>> Although I'm a little fat. I better I
better get like a new suit.
>> I've lost another seven pounds in the
last two weeks.
>> Well, that's not you. Yeah, but I don't
recommend your diet plan.
>> No, you you saw what I ate this weekend.
Yeah, I I I definitely did. I hope I
mean, you just got another few weeks.
It's going to be rough, but All right.
So, John, you're muted, FYI. Uh I hope
you know that. You're muted. There you
go.
>> Um
>> Okay. Yeah. Whatever. Okay. We're We're
back. All right. So, let's see. Um Okay.
So, Trump doesn't want us to vote by
mail and he doesn't want us to vote by
machines. John, how does he want us to
vote? Does he want us to vote at all
>> if it's for him? And I'll tell you,
I I'm worried about that. Yeah. You and
I discussed this over the weekend. Um
he's like seriously telling people he's
considering a third term. Uh Steve
Bannon said last week Trump will run for
a third term. He can't run for a third
term. Now, today I heard on on I I can't
remember whether it was MSNBC or or CNN
that uh Republicans are talking about
repealing the what was it, Ted? The 22nd
amendment. The 24th amendment. 22nd
amendment.
>> Yeah, I think it's I want to say 20
>> I think 24, right? I think I'm not sure.
>> 24th that limits presidents to two
elected terms. Um that's not going to be
possible. They only said that because
most Americans don't know how
constitutional amendments are passed,
right? You have to have twothirds of the
House,
>> twothirds of the Senate,
then the president signs it, then it
goes to the states,
>> and then you have to get three quarters
>> of all the states
>> to pass it in their legislatures by
twothirds and twothirds.
>> Correct. in five years,
>> right? Which is why the E is not
>> not gonna happen. Yeah.
>> Not gonna happen.
>> Yeah. And not to mention anyway
elections I think we can dispose of this
with the following statement. Uh the the
uh elections are managed by the states,
not by the federal government. Period.
Full stop. So I don't think there's any
Trump can say whatever he wants. He
doesn't get to do anything about this.
Um all right. So this is uh I thought a
weird story. Um, you know, following the
uh brief 12-day war between Israel and
Iran, um, Iran clearly had a major
espionage problem, as you and I have
talked about, a lot of people were
recruited online, uh, like for really
small amounts of money to sabotage, uh,
you know, on behalf of the Israelis. Um,
now the the Iranians appear to be in a
full-fledged purge mode where they've
rounded up 20,000 people as possible
spies for Israel. Um, is that
>> 20,000 people?
>> It's not possible that they're all
guilty, right?
>> No. No. Is this a Is this just a
basically like a ICE style roundup? You
just grab everyone you can and let God
sort them out later.
>> Yeah. The Iranian press reported today
that most of these people are ethnic
Afghans.
>> They're Afghan reg refugees. what the
what the Iranians are accusing the
Israelis of having done was to target um
undocumented Afghan refugees in Iran
only because over the last two years the
Iranians have been expelling them back
to Afghanistan.
And so there's the Israelis are saying
what loyalty should you have to the
Iranians? They don't want you. They
don't like you. They're trying to give
you back to the Taliban. You should work
for us. We'll give you a $100 a month if
you work for us. And all we want you to
do is tell us where you're seeing
Iranian troop movements, where the
Iranian nuclear scientists live, uh, you
know, what are the addresses of the
electrical company and the water company
headquarters. And so, uh, I mean, that's
cheap intelligence.
>> I mean, you know, and you can sort of
see like you and I know Afghans. I mean,
you know, Afghans aren't for sale, but
they're definitely for rent.
>> For rent. Exactly. And you can always,
you know, and and that's how that's kind
of like cultural and they're kind of
used to it because of all the occupiers
that have been passing through to and
fro forever.
>> Yes.
>> And but they but I mean I I will say
>> um to my Afghan listeners that were
considering to do this, like come on,
this is the Iranians provided you
hospitality. You know that that's
everything. I mean, they provided
generous hospitality for you guys. Not
everyone wants you, you know. It's not
it's no way to repay them.
>> Ted RT is reporting right now several
things that I think are important.
>> Cool.
>> Um Trump
interrupted his meeting with European
leaders just just now to call Putin.
We don't know what the call was about.
Trump said, "In a week or two, we'll
know whether this can be solved."
And then he said,
um,
I'm sorry. Then the Financial Times
reported that Ukraine just announced 11
minutes ago that it will buy $100
billion dollar of US weapons. it will
buy them.
The purchase will be financed by the
European Union and in exchange, the
United States will promise to defend
Ukraine against Russia.
I'm not even sure I understand what that
means.
>> Well, it sounds this is a typical Trump
type deal, right? I mean where basically
he's saying we will defend you but you
have you have to pay us for the
privilege.
>> Yeah. You have to pay us.
>> Yeah.
>> But the thing is is how do we defend
Ukraine in a way that is not a violation
of the NATO charter and invite Russian
response?
>> What do you mean by that?
>> Well,
the United States is a member of NATO.
If the United States goes to to protect
Ukraine, there's a Russian attack. The
United States attacks Russia. Russia
retaliates. It has to retaliate by
attacking the United States.
>> But the NATO charter says an attack on
one. It is an attack on all. And then
all of a sudden
>> NATO's at war with Russia.
>> Yeah. I mean, we come full circle,
right? I mean, this is, you know, what I
was saying before. Putin was right to
demand that Ukraine not join NATO.
>> Yeah. and and and like calling it, you
know, dressing it up and calling it
something else, you know, article five
like protections is just sophistry and
and it's not going to work.
>> Hey, uh Star Lion is is reminding us to
talk about uh about this Israeli the the
head of Israeli cyber defense in the
United States was arrested in Las Vegas
uh Saturday and charged with multiple
counts of child pornography. He was
immediately allowed to leave and he got
on a plane and flew back to Israel. Why?
Because Israel does not extradite Jews.
>> Yeah. His name is Tom Artium
Alexandrovich.
He's a senior cyber security official
>> who was basically ins snared in an
undercover sting operation by the local
cops targeting child sex predators. So
he sounds like he's accused of being a
lovely fellow.
Yeah. Um, and what about the victims? I
mean, presumably these victims are
American children.
>> By the way, um, thank you so much to
Pedro Louise Taff on the Rumble Feed for
gifting a membership
>> to um, NPC3PO.
>> Thank you for that. And to Tusk PC, is
it possible that the CIA mathematics
department created Bitcoin? Yeah, it's
possible. I' I've heard that a couple
the mysterious Japanese uh professor.
>> I I actually do think it's the
mysterious Japanese professor and and I
think that's why the American government
has scrambled since the creation of
Bitcoin to make sure that they force
Americans to admit whether they have
bought or sold Bitcoin at tax time
because they really are panicking that
they can't track it all. But I I could
see the CIA being in some way involved
with Bitcoin. Sure.
>> Yeah. Like the CIA often has to create.
I mean, I thought it was fascinating.
>> It's not Thoria, right? What's the
satellite phone company that the CIA
bought
>> because it was in trouble?
>> The the Gutteries um made Thoria phone.
The CIA bought Intel Sat.
>> Yeah, there was a different It's a
different name. Um
>> Oh, you sure?
>> Yeah, I'm sure. And it's like Yeah. And
there were It was going to go out of
business. It was an unprofitable
company, but the CIA needed those the
Yeah, it's going to come to me. I I know
because I had to rent that those phones
when I went to Afghanistan. They were
big.
>> I had a Thoria phone when I went to
Afghanistan.
>> Well, those are good. They're better.
>> I liked it.
>> Yeah. Smaller. Um
Well, while we're figuring that out,
it'll come. It'll come. Um Jonathan
Pard, there's a name we haven't heard
for a while.
So, uh, maybe we'll wrap it up with him.
Uh, so, yeah, we'll get into the Israel
news, right? So, basically, the Israelis
are are never been less popular. And
this isn't going to help. Jonathan Pard,
maybe you should explain who Jonathan
Pard was.
>> Jonathan Pard was a traitor. Jonathan
Pard was a US Navy intelligence officer
who in 1985 was arrested and charged
with espionage for giving um top secret
top secret NSA and DoD documents to
Israel. As if that wasn't bad enough,
these documents were all about Soviet
military movements, and the Israelis
gave them to the Soviet Union in
exchange for the Soviets releasing a
handful of Russian Jews to Israel. Pard
was caught, he was convicted, and he was
sentenced to 30 years in prison, which
was the maximum for what he had been
charged for. Um,
literally every single time an Israeli
leader came to the United States, he
would ask the president from Ronald
Reagan to Joe Biden to release Pard to
Israel. Um, Bill Clinton almost did it
and and George Tennant said, "If you do
it, I'm going to resign and the entire
leadership of the CIA is going to
resign." and we're going to go public
and say why we resigned. And so Clinton
changed his mind. Finally, when Pard did
the entire 30 years, he was released.
The Israeli government sent a plane to
the United States. The plane picked him
up and carried him back to Israel where
there there was a parade for him. They
named the street after him.
>> He was a hero.
>> Big hero. Big hero.
>> Well, now he's running for parliament.
>> And will he be elected? Will he make it
to the Knesset? He doesn't even know
what party he's going to be in.
>> Because he's not a member of a party.
I'm going to say no. He's not going to
make it because there are very very few
independents that are able that are able
to win. You have to win a certain
percentage. It's like 3% or I think it's
3%. And and na of the national vote and
it's going to be tough for him. But if
he if he's picked up by one of the by
one of the Zionist uh parties or one of
the Russian parties, yeah, he could
he'll probably end up in in uh in the
Knesset. Makes me sick to my stomach.
>> I'm just I was just going to ask you how
this makes you feel. Um and I guess we
could just talk we have two quick quick
things. Democrats are back in Texas
>> and it looks like basically all the a
bunch of states both Republican and
Democratic are just going to do play
redistricting games. Um and um and
basically they're going to try to see
how far ahead they can get.
>> Is this going to become like the new
normal? Like year after year we're
constantly going to be redistricting and
this is how we're going to play out our
elections with the voters is a sideshow.
>> I I suspect it is. I I think this is
this is the state of our politics now
where it's all about politics. It's not
at all about policy. And so
>> thank you Fasmatas. Yes. Iridium. That's
the phone company.
>> Iridium. I remember them.
Um, so I think that Texas is going to is
going to wipe out five Democratic House
seats. California is going to wipe out
five Republican House seats. Uh, I think
Ohio is going to wipe out one or two
Dems and New York's going to wipe out a
Republican. Uh, probably I uh I I'm
sorry, Illinois is going to wipe out two
or three Republicans. Maybe Nebraska's
gonna try to wipe out that one
Democratic seat in Omaha. So, yeah, I
think this is the new normal. And may I
ask answer one question? I know we're
totally out of time.
>> Sure. Sure.
>> Did we hear about the Putin poop
suitcase to bring his poop back to
Russia from the Alaska meeting?
>> That is actually not uncommon.
>> What?
>> That is not That is not at all uncommon.
Many leaders who come to the United
States collect their own feces to take
back and dispose of in their own toilets
because there are entities within the US
government that will gladly happily
collect that poop
>> for the for the DNA
>> for the DNA and the health information.
>> Wow.
So, some poor slob at the uh hotel has
to uh scoop it out of the toilet, I
assume.
>> Yeah, but the poor slob at the hotel is
really a CIA officer undercover as a
hotel employee.
>> It's like the good news is you've got a
job at the CIA. The bad news is this is
your job at the CIA.
>> Um, yeah. Would you have taken that job,
John, or would you have resigned?
No, I'd say no. You got to draw the line
somewhere. You have to have some
self-respect.
>> Listen, I there are a lot of things that
I did for my country, and that's that's
not one of them.
>> Uh, thank you.
>> Last not least, quickly, Paris is
preparing for 50° C, 122° Fahrenheit uh
temperatures. I mean I you know when it
was Lutess when it was a Roman city uh
Paris was an assignment um that was a
low a low prestige assignment because
the weather kind of sucks in Paris.
People don't really realize that uh or
they don't think about it a lot but it
never sucked like this. Europe is uh
really going to be suffering major
climate change issues in the very near
future. Um and it seems like they're I
mean I guess they're at least they're
preparing for it in a way that we're
not.
>> Um I don't know. Any thoughts?
>> No, I think this is I think you're
exactly right. Um, you know, it's funny
to me, too, that Tulsi Gabbard came out
and said that we're facing a climate
disaster. And I wonder if she was the
one who was chosen by the administration
to begin bringing conservatives around.
>> A lot of people are going to die.
>> Well, that's true, right? Like bringing
conservatives around, there's a lot
That's something that I mean, I'm really
glad you put it that way. RFK. When did
when on earth did conservatives care
about eating well and a good diet? When
did that happen? Suddenly like, oh, and
this make America healthy again. We were
always like the health. No, you weren't.
That's like a crunchy lefty thing.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Right. A crunchy lefty
thing. It shouldn't be. on board. You
know,
>> you know, when I went to Alaska with
Gary Johnson back in 2016, we went to
see this glacier and you go to the
visitors center and then they give you
the little briefing and the glacier is
like a quarter of a mile away. Well, the
glacier used to go right up to the
visitor center. That's why they put the
visitor center there. You could reach
out and touch the glacier from the from
the observation deck. And somebody said,
"Why would they put the visitor center
so far away from the glacier?" Haha.
Well, no, that's not that's not funny.
That's not funny at all. This is exactly
what we should be talking about.
>> Always. All right. So, um I guess that's
we're I think that's going to do it,
guys. It's very exciting. We're here
tomorrow, Tuesday, and Wednesday and
Thursday and Friday. That's right. We're
five days a week as promised starting
now. So, please show the love, like,
follow, and share the show. Um, really
love doing this every day. I'm looking
forward to hanging out with you every
day, John. So,
>> me too, Ted.
>> Like, follow, and share. Those are the
words of the day. Thanks, everyone.
We'll see you tomorrow.
[Music]